Sector 72, Noida, India 🙃

6290639790 📞

Arunpratap26@yahoo.com ■

www.linkedin.com/in/arunpratap26 in

arunpratap26.github.io/

# **ARUN KUMAR SINGH** SOFTWARE ENGINEER



#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Focused and quick-learning Software Engineer with 2.9 years of experience in programming and web design for various projects and clients. I am also skilled in requirements analysis and project documentation. I have ability to work in team as well as in group, I always keep myself updated with latest trends and technology and I am looking for a company with good work culture where I can contribute for company and grow myself.



## **SKILLS**

- C#
- Asp.Net
- Asp.Net MVC
- Asp.Net Core
- Entity Framework
- SQL
- LINQ
- Visual studio
- TFS

- JavaScript
- jQuery
- bootstrap
- Git
- GitHub
- SQL Server
- NPM
- Visual studio code



# LEARNING /INTRESTED

NodeJS, ReactJS, AngularJS, Blazor.



# EXPERIENCE

# Software Engineer | Chetu India, Noida

JUL 2019 - PRESENT

Here I am working as a software engineer and I worked on some US based clients project which assigned to me and attended client meeting also demonstrate weekly task to client and push my code to TFS, I am learning several things here and updating myself with challenging environment.

## Dot Net Developer | Kazma Technology, Kolkata

DEC 2018 - JUN 2019

I worked on several projects with great team and explored more latest technologies and trends also found a good mentor who always motivated me to push some extra mile for my projects as well as my career and goals. Some of projects which I built here are Jain furnishing, Vship crm, Weerp.

## Dot Net Developer | Medtelerad Healthcare, Kolkata

JUL 2017 - NOV 2018

I started my career with Medtelerad Healthcare and built several modern healthcare applications and contributed in several parts of decision making as it was a startup so I worked from starting face of Medtelerad products and as I was just 2<sup>nd</sup> employee in development team so I learnt a lot of things there. Some of the product which I built here are Medtelerad PACS, Spandan PACS, Addenex PACS.



#### **EDUCATION**

**BCA** | Naraina Group of institution, Kanpur

2013 - 2016

59.9%

12<sup>th</sup> (Physics, Chemistry, Math) | Gopeshwar college, Hathua

2011 - 2013

69.8%

10<sup>th</sup> | SPNHS, Raghua -Jamsar

2011

65.8%